[Music]
[Praise]
Hello, Hello,
from 18 to 75 years, any
individual or family
can take a presence policy and if I talk about children, then we
need such dependents,
you can do it as many times as you need,
secondly, there is no hundred percent
exhaust and no condition, the
restoration is actually general, if we short it from partial then also
your insurance will be reduced, if any person
needs it then also it will be reduced,
now amazing amazing features friends,
another great thing is your delivery
expenses, after 2 years there is delivery expense cover
and that too for 10% off deposit, genuinely
amazing feature, your consumable items
are covered, lawn console, whatever else, you have to
pay charges under it, you will
not have to pay here, 68 non-items
are covered here, generally it is a good feature, apart from this, from
new born to
new born baby up to Rs. 400000 will be covered in it
and the new born week date is only
one year  There is a waiting period if you want to get IVF treatment done, then
that is covered here which is only
2 years waiting period
is a very good and wonderful feature, apart from this,
here you get cumulative bonus along with no claim bonus, the
bonus will not be reduced here if a claim comes, in all other
plans your current affair bonus gets
reduced as soon as it comes, this will not happen here, you will
get 25% bonus every year and in the year in which there is
no claim and the maximum will go up to 100%, amazing amazing,
you will get to see many such wonderful features in the policy here, I
hope you have understood the content video,
hello your friend
Yogendra